你好
Hello?
停止不要动
Stop. Don't move.
他们可以看到我们
They can see us.
这是什么？
What is this?
我不知道
I don't know.
- 我们在哪里？ - 你觉得呢？
- Where are we? - Where do you think?
你好
Hello?
哦 我的上帝！
Oh, my God!
没事的 好吗？没关系
It's all right, okay? It's all right.
- 你没事 - 帮助帮助
-You're okay. -Help! Help!
- 冷静点  - 厕所
- Just calm down. - John.
- 你没事 - 你在哪？
-You're fine. -Where are you?
哦 见鬼
Oh, shit.
她死了吗？
Is she dead?
我认为是这样
I think so.
耶稣基督 那是什么？
Jesus Christ. What was that?
我不知道
I don't know.
那是什么？
What was that?
倒霉
Shit.
卧槽？
What the fuck?
- 大家都别动！ - 哦 我的上帝
- Everyone freeze! - Oh, my God.
他们可以看到我们是否移动
They can see if we move.
别动 我们会没事的
Stand still and we'll be fine.
不要把脚抬离地面
Don't lift your feet off the ground.
不要碰任何人
Don't touch anyone.
- 那是什么声音 - 嘘
-What's that noise? -Shh.
哦 我的上帝
Oh, my God.
- 那是从哪里来的 - 轻声的
-Where's that coming from? -Quiet!
好的 现在
Okay, now...
- 冷静下来 冷静点  - 这没用
- Calm down. Calm down. - It's no use.
- 苏珊 - 布鲁斯？
-Susan. -Bruce?
大家冷静下来
Everybody calm down.
你们需要冷静下来 伙计们
You need to calm down, guys.
大家冷静下来！
Everybody calm the fuck down!
只是想想 呼吸
Just... just think, breathe.
到底是怎么回事？
What the hell is going on?
不 不
No. No.
我们来了
Here we go.
大家都闭嘴！
Everybody shut up for one second!
有人知道这到底是怎么回事吗？
Does anybody know what the hell's going on?
- 他们要杀了我们 - 不 不是他们
- They're killing us. - No, it's not them.
你们看到了吗？
Are you guys seeing this?
地板上的灯 你看到它动了吗？
The lights on the floor. You see it move?
- 我什么都没看见 - 在那边
-I don't see anything. -Over there.
- 你在说什么？ - 看看你的手
- What are you talking about? - Look at your hands.
当你移动它们时 它会改变地板
When you move 'em, it changes the floor.
哦 见鬼 是的
Oh, shit, yeah.
我只看到一个
I only see one.
是的 我只看到我的
Yeah, I only see mine.
我想你只能看到自己的
I think you can only see your own.
他们对我们做了什么？
What did they do to us?
- 我想他们弄乱了我们的手  - 这是什么意思？
- I think they messed with our hands. - -What does that mean?
- 是我们 - 我们？
- It's us. - Us?
- 你什么意思？ - 我们在选择谁死
- What do you mean? - We're choosing who dies.
- 操！ - 怎么搞的？
- Fuck! - What happened?
- 有人干了  - 没人他妈的干什么
- Somebody did it. - -Nobody fucking do anything.
嗯 它不起作用 你明白吗？
Well, it's not working, you see?
- 我们得试试看  - 没人做！
- We have to try something. - Nobody do it!
可以
Okay.
- 该死的 - 什么鬼？
- Goddamn it. - What the hell?
你们这些人怎么了？
What is wrong with you people?
我们所有人都会死的 我们所有人都会死的
All of us, we're gonna die. All of us, we're gonna die.
我们都完蛋了
We're all fucked.
哦 我的上帝
Oh, my God.
这是难以置信的
This is unbelievable.
- 这是投票  - 什么
- It's a vote. - What?
我们正在投票 听着 他们在杀得票最多的人
We're voting. Look, they're killing whoever gets the most votes.
你怎么知道的？
How do you know that?
因为因为当你闭上你的手时 铃声就响了
Because... Because the chimes go off when you close your hands,
这是你选择的时候
and that's when you choose.
- 我们应该尽量不要再做了  - 算了吧
- We should try not doing it again. - -Forget it.
- 有人会搞砸的  - 等待
- Someone's gonna screw it up. - Wait.
如果我们   如果我们再次投票给她呢？
What if we... What if we vote for her again?
- 是的 我们试试看 好吗？ - 伙计们 这不是
- Yeah, let's try that, okay? - Guys, that's not...
- 不 这行不通  - 我们必须尝试一下
- No, it's not gonna work. - -We have to try something.
是的 各位 让我们再次投票给那个死去的女人
Yeah, everybody, let's vote for the dead woman again.
- 真的吗 - 你是认真的吗？
-Really? -Are you serious?
来吧 来吧
Come on. Come on.
- 你们选错人了 - 不 我们没有
-You guys picked the wrong person. -No, we didn't.
- 伙计们 这不管用  - 但为什么是他？
- Guys, it just doesn't work. - -But why him?
也许他得票第二多
Maybe he got the second most votes.
还是迄今为止最重要的？
Or the most so far?
- 我们必须尝试一下 - 不 不行 伙计们 好吗？
-We have to try something. -No, it's not gonna work, guys, okay?
我们无能为力 我们都完蛋了
There's nothing we can do. We're all screwed.
- 让我们试着不再投票 - 请
-Let's try not voting again. -Please.
- 这行不通  - 我们需要尝试
- It's not gonna work. - We need to try.
好吧 没人投票 让我们等一下
Okay, nobody vote. Let's wait it out.
我们怎么知道这不会杀死我们所有人？
How do we know that won't kill us all?
十 九 八 七
Ten, nine, eight, seven,
六 五 四 三
six, five, four, three...
结束了吗？
Is it over?
- 哦 我的上帝 - 好了 没人动
-Oh, my God! -Okay, nobody move.
只是 大家 让我们骑出去
Just, everybody, let's ride this out.
如果我们不选择 它会自己选择
If we don't choose, it chooses on its own.
有人需要做点什么 这显然行不通
Somebody needs to do something. This is not working, obviously.
- 你说的没道理 - 大家安静！
-What you said, that didn't make sense. -Everybody quiet!
现在 没有理由
Now, there's no reason
让我们大家都这样互相残杀
for us all to just keep killing each other off like this.
好吧 我们还能做什么 伙计？
Well, what the hell else are we gonna do, my man?
我们别无选择
We don't have a choice.
我的意思是 我们可以选择以某种方式来解决这个问题
What I mean is we can choose to go about this in a certain way.
看 所以每一轮之间大约有一两分钟
Look, so there's about a minute or two between each round.
- 这不是很多时间 - 是的 没什么
-That's not a lot of time. -Yeah, no shit.
也许如果我们少花点时间担心谁会死
Maybe if we spend less time worrying about who's gonna die next
还有更多的时间试图弄清楚这件事
and more time trying to figure this thing out,
我们会找到一个地方 能够阻止这一切
we'll get somewhere and be able to stop this.
你有什么建议？
What do you suggest?
好吧 我一直在绕圈子
Okay, I've been looking round the circle
我明白了   五六个七八十岁的人
and I see... five or six people in their 70s and 80s.
如果这是投票 我说他们先投票 那会为我们争取一些时间
If this a vote, I say they go first. That'll buy us some time.
- 等等  - 不 不 见鬼 不 伙计
- Wait a second. - No, no. Hell, no, man.
你是认真的吗？
Are you serious?
听着 在我看来 他们是下一个在现实生活中死去的人 对吧？
Look, the way I see it, they'd be the next people to die in real life, right?
- 有什么不同 - 他是对的 老人优先
-What's the difference? -He's right. Old people first.
那是   这很公平
That's... That's fair.
- 这公平吗 - 无论如何 他们会是下一个死亡的人
-How is that fair? -They'd be the next to die anyway.
是的 是自然的原因 而不是我们杀了他们
Yeah, of natural causes, not of us killing them.
- 有什么不同 - 这太疯狂了
-What's the difference? -This is crazy.
- 我们别无选择 - 搞砸了 孩子
-We have no choice. -That's fucked up, kid.
这是一个糟糕的情况 但我们必须做些什么
It's a fucked-up situation, but we have to do something.
哪一个先？
Which one first?
我们从他开始 然后顺时针走
We'll start with him, go clockwise after that.
一 二 三
One, two, three...
不 等等
No, wait a minute.
…四 五 六
...four, five, six.
那应该能给我们十分钟的时间
That should buy us ten minutes.
不 不 不 必须有另一种方法
No. No, no. There has to be another way.
你有更好的主意吗？
You have a better idea?
任何人
Anyone?
我很抱歉 这是唯一的办法
I'm sorry. It's the only way.
但我和你们一样有生存的权利
But I have just as much of a right to live as any of you.
你过得很好 老人
You've lived your life, old man.
请
Please.
Please!
可以我知道这很难
Okay. I know that was hard.
但你们都做了正确的事
But you all did the right thing.
我们必须做出一些艰难的决定
We're gonna have to make some difficult decisions.
闭嘴 好吗？我们明白了
Just shut up, all right? We get it.
你想争取一些时间 我们做到了 我们不要浪费它
You wanted to buy some time and we did that. Let's not waste it.
让我们弄清楚这到底是什么 有什么想法吗？
Let's figure out what the hell this is. Any ideas?
来吧 有人吗？
Come on. Somebody?
- 他呢 - 谁 我？
-What about him? -Who, me?
是 啊我是说 你应该对此有所了解
Yeah. I mean, you ought to know something about this.
- 我什么都不知道 - 瞎扯
-I don't know anything. -Bullshit.
- 是的 是的 你们必须知道 - 知道什么吗？
-Yeah, yeah, you guys had to know. -Know about what?
那他妈的外星人入侵呢？我不知道
What about a fucking alien invasion? I don't know.
- 什么 - 听着 我知道的和你一样多
-What? -Look, I know just as much as you do.
- 胡说 伙计  - 我发誓 我什么都不知道
- Bullshit, man. - I swear, I don't know anything.
有人还记得什么吗？
Does anybody remember anything else?
我在格伦代尔
I was in Glendale.
是的 我知道
Yeah, I do.
我们在高速公路上堵车了
We were stuck in traffic on the freeway.
- 我也是  - 我也是
- Me too. - So was I.
正确的
Right.
我们正试图离开这座城市 但这是一个完全的木材堵塞
We were trying to get out of the city, but it was a total log jam,
于是我们下车开始跑步
so we got out of the car and started running.
是 是 是 每个人都在跑步
Yeah, yeah, yeah. Everybody was running.
是的 然后   然后一切都变黑了
Yeah, and then... and then everything went dark.
这就是我记得的
That's what I remember.
- 那发生了什么？ - 我被拉上来了
- So what happened? - I was pulled up.
- 进入飞船？ - 我…我不知道
- Into the ship? - I... I don't know.
- 拖拉机梁 - 性交
-Tractor beam. -Fuck.
我们现在在船上吗？
So are we in the ship now?
你认为还有其他人在做这件事吗？
Do you think there are other people doing this?
其他圆圈？
Other circles?
他们不会为我们50个人经历这一切
They wouldn't go through all this for 50 of us.
他们为什么要这样做？
Why would they do this?
我不知道 但下一次我能看见的时候 我在一个小房间里
I don't know. But the next time that I could see, I was in a small room
一切都是红色的 就像   像一个黑暗的房间
and everything was red, like... like a dark room,
还有一大堆尸体堆积在一起
and there were a ton of bodies piled up on one another.
我…我以为他们已经死了
I... I assumed that they were dead,
但是 我不知道 他们可能只是昏迷了
but, I don't know, they might have just been unconscious.
除了我和另外一个人以外 所有人
Everybody but me and one other guy.
- 外星人？ - 不 不 不 他是一个人
- An alien? - No. No, no, no. He was a human.
- 谁？我们中的一个 - 我不知道 我没看到他在这里
-Who? One of us? -I don't know. I don't see him in here.
其他一切都有点模糊
Everything else is kind of a blur.
我只记得醒来的时候这里有一些气体
I just remember waking up right here and there was some kind of gas.
我…我想我们都被下药了
I... I think that we were all drugged.
还有人记得什么吗？
Does anybody else remember anything?
来吧 任何人
Come on, anybody.
是的 是的 我知道
Yeah, yeah, I do.
- 你 - 是 啊
-You? -Yeah.
我记得那个红色的房间
I remember the red room.
我看到了他
And I saw him.
我看到了他们
And I saw them.
他们长什么样？
Well, what did they look like?
嗯 它们 呃 又大又黑
Well, they were, er, big and black.
也许是深绿色
Dark green, maybe.
和和并且潮湿
And... and... and wet.
他们也说话了 听起来几乎像中国人
And they spoke too. It sounded almost like Chinese.
- 中文？ - 是的 中国人
- Chinese? - Yeah, Chinese.
也许是日本人
Or Japanese maybe.
- 中国外星人？ - 瞎扯
- Chinese aliens? - Bullshit.
他在撒谎
He's lying.
是的 他是下一个 他只是想争取时间
Yeah, he's next in line. He's just trying to buy some time.
不 我发誓 告诉他们 告诉他们你看见我了
No, I swear. Tell them. Tell them you saw me.
- 你看到了吗？他全是狗屎 - 我发誓 我说的是实话
-You see? He's full of shit. -I swear, I'm telling the truth.
给我点时间想想
Just give me some time to think.
这是一个骗局 不要相信他
It's a trick. Don't believe him.
它又回到我身边了 它又回来了
It's coming back to me. It's coming back.
数字 我记得数字
Numbers. I remember numbers.
还有一件事 他们
And there was something else that they...
- 现在 我们在哪里 - 等待下一位是谁？
-Now, where were we? -Wait. Who's next in line?
她戴着帽子
Her. With the hat.
- 谁 我 - 是 啊
-Who, me? -Yeah.
- 你多大了 - 52.
-How old are you? -52.
- 这不老了 - 够老了
-That's not old. -Old enough.
嘿 我们说70或80 而不是50
Hey, we said 70 or 80, not 50.
有什么不同？
What's the difference?
- 这是一个很大的区别 - 来吧 女士 你不是52岁
-That's a big difference. -Come on, lady, you're not 52.
- 你多大了 - 不要撒谎
-How old are you? -Don't lie.
- 我52岁 - 瞎扯
-I'm 52. -Bullshit.
是 啊为什么你的头发这么白？
Yeah. Why is your hair so white?
化疗我得了癌症
Chemotherapy. I had cancer.
那你不应该是秃头吗？
Aren't you supposed to be bald, then?
- 什么样的癌症 - 乳腺癌症
-What kind of cancer? -Breast cancer.
- 那么你快死了 - 不 病情缓解了
-So you're dying, then? -No. It's in remission.
我现在好多了
I'm better now.
你确定吗？
Are you sure?
是 啊我赢了
Yeah. I beat it.
- 但它可能会回来 - 你他妈的怎么了？
-It could come back, though. -What the fuck is wrong with you?
我只是说 她比我们其他人更有可能死亡
I'm just saying, she's more likely to die than the rest of us.
- 这不是真的 - 你是什么 医生 女士？
-That's not true. -What are you, a doctor, lady?
事实上 是的 我是 混蛋
Actually, yes, I am, asshole.
听着 不管是不是癌症 她已经50多岁了 她最终不得不离开
Look, cancer or not, she's over 50. She's gonna have to go eventually.
什么
What?
- 我们从未同意这一点 - 是的 不可能 伙计
-We never agreed to that. -Yeah, no way, man.
我们下一步要开始屠杀40岁以上的人吗？
Are we gonna start killing off people over 40 next?
我43岁 你想杀了我吗 混蛋？
I'm 43. You wanna kill me next, asshole?
- 嘿 你有问题吗 - 是的 我有个问题
-Hey, you got a problem? -Yeah, I got a problem.
我想可能有人超过这个年龄
I think maybe anyone over the age
也许 我不知道 35岁可能有问题
of maybe, I don't know, 35 might have a problem.
你们觉得怎么样？
What do you guys think?
听着 嘿 现在 等一下
Look, hey, now, just hold on a second.
让我们
Let's...
我只是想帮忙
I'm just trying to help.
操你
Fuck you.
听着 我们不能害怕在这里互相交谈
Listen, we can't be afraid to talk to each other in here.
这是我们想办法阻止这一切的唯一方法
It's the only way we're gonna figure out how to stop this.
哦 伙计 我们不会阻止的 我们只是被操了
Oh, man, we're not gonna stop this. We're just fucked.
- 我们不知道  - 确切地我们还什么都不知道
- We don't know that. - Exactly. We don't know anything yet.
如果他们想杀我们 他们早就这么做了 但他们没有
If they wanted to kill us, they would have done that already, but they didn't.
所以 让我们利用这段时间 找出原因
So let's use this time and try and figure out why.
可以我们该怎么做？
Okay. What do we do?
也许我们应该弄清楚他们为什么选择我们
Maybe we should figure out why they chose us.
- 选择我们？ - 是 啊
- Chose us? - Yeah.
他们为什么选择我们来这里
Why they picked us to be in here.
这是一个巨大的太空真空 我不认为我们是人工挑选的
It was a giant space vacuum. I don't think we were hand-picked.
不 他是对的 这是…这只是随机的
No, he's right. This is... This is just random.
我们不知道 也许这不是随机的
We don't know that. Maybe it wasn't random.
也许他们选择我们是有原因的
Maybe they chose us for a reason.
可能有无数人在做我们现在正在做的事情
There's probably a zillion people doing the same thing we're doing right now.
好吧 但这里只有我们 对吧？
Okay, but it's just us in here, right?
我认为我们需要更多地了解彼此
I think we need to know more about each other.
也许如果我们
Maybe if we do...
这一切都有道理
this will all make sense.
值得一试 有人想开始吗？
It's worth a shot. Anybody wanna start?
是 啊我先去 你好我是贝丝
Yeah. I'll go first. Hi. I'm Beth.
嗯   我住在加利福尼亚州伍德兰山
Erm... I live in Woodland Hills, California,
但最初我来自弗吉尼亚州里士满 出生并长大
but originally I'm from Richmond, Virginia, born and raised.
我在人力资源部门工作了11年
I've worked in human resources for the past 11 years.
我只是有点陷入其中
I just kind of fell into it.
我上大学是为了主修英语
I actually went to college to be an English major.
弗吉尼亚大学 去吧 瓦胡斯
University of Virginia. Go, Wahoos.
我36岁 单身 没有孩子
I'm 36, single, no kids,
但我确实有两个侄子来自我姐姐诺琳
but I do have two nephews from my sister Noreen.
她实际上是我的双胞胎妹妹 还有什么？
She's actually my twin sister. What else?
哦 我有一条狗 她的名字叫克洛蒂 是一个混血儿
Oh, I have a dog. Her name is Clootie and she's a terrier mix.
我有两只猫 JJ和Ricky
And I have two cats, JJ and Ricky.
哦 我的上帝
Oh, my God.
我想就是这样了 我还有什么要说的吗？
I think that's about it. Is there anything else I should say?
不 太好了 干得好 谁想下一个去？
No, that's great. Great job. Who wants to go next?
性交！
Fuck!
- 至少她没有孩子 - 是的 是的
-At least she didn't have kids. -Yeah, yeah.
- 我就是这么想的 - 我也是
-That's what I was thinking. -Me too.
那又怎么样？这没关系
So what? That doesn't matter.
她和你们一样还是一个人
She was still a human being just like any of you.
- 她叫什么名字？ - 贝丝
- What was her name? - Beth.
也许我们不该说出自己的名字
Maybe we shouldn't say our names.
为什么不呢？
Why not?
它有什么帮助？
How does it help?
那么 谈话有什么意义呢？
What's the point in talking at all, then?
不 没有名字 他是对的
No, no names, he's right.
我们不需要比现在更困难
We don't need to make this harder than it already is.
是的 是的 我是说 如果是匿名的 那就是
Yeah, yeah. I mean, if it's anonymous, it's...
什么更容易杀死所有人？
What? Easier to kill everyone?
这不是我要说的
That's not what I was gonna say.
- 那我就说出来 - 没关系
-I'll say it, then. -It doesn't matter.
名字不是必须的
Names aren't necessary.
其他人应该发言 你呢？
Someone else should speak. How about you?
- 我 - 是的 你是下一个
-Me? -Yeah, you're next in line.
好吧 他妈的 伙计 我没说什么
Well, fuck that, man. I ain't saying shit.
你看到了她身上发生的事 她没有说什么错
You seen what happened to her and she didn't say nothing wrong.
嗯 应该有人说话
Well, someone should speak.
好的 我会的 我会尽量保持简短
Okay, I will. I'll try to keep this short.
- 我叫克雷格… - 嘿 没有名字
- My name's Craig... - Hey, no names.
正确的我很抱歉
Right. I'm sorry.
总之 我说什么的原因
Anyway, the reason I'm saying anything
是因为我妻子站在我旁边
is because my wife is standing next to me.
我认为这很重要 这不可能只是巧合 对吧？
I thought that would be important. That can't just be a coincidence, right?
其他人有关系吗？任何人
Is anyone else related? Anybody?
- 认识吗？ - 对
- Know each other? - Yes.
我认识她 苏珊
I know her. Susan.
怎样
How?
- 我们是呃…同事 - 邻居
-We're, er... co-workers. -Neighbors.
不要介意 这并不重要
Never mind. It's not important.
公共事务知道了
Affair. Got it.
无论如何 我只是想恭敬地问大家
Anyway, I just wanted to ask everyone respectfully,
请不要投票给我妻子
please don't vote for my wife.
你可以投票给我 但请原谅我的妻子
You can vote for me, but please just spare my wife.
不
No.
不 每个人都会考虑到这一点
No, everyone will take that into consideration.
好的 谢谢
Okay, thanks.
呃……好的 你下一个去
Er... Okay. You go next.
来吧 走吧 嘿 你会说英语吗？
Come on, go. Hey, you speak English?
哦 他走了
Oh, well, he's gone.
没关系 我会说西班牙语
It's okay. I speak Spanish.
我们不需要他妈的翻译
We don't need a fucking translator.
是的 我很抱歉 但他是对的 这是浪费时间
Yeah, I'm sorry, but he's right, it's a waste of time.
不 不是
No, it's not.
- 他在说什么 - 看见这已经在浪费时间了
- What's he saying? -See? It's already wasting time.
不 不是 我们都是人
No, it's not. We're all human beings.
是的 我们在这里都是一样的
Yeah, we all count the same in here.
我们不应该杀别人
We shouldn't kill someone else
甚至无法参与对话的人
over someone who can't even contribute to the conversation.
他是对的 这不公平
He's right. That's not fair.
我的意思是 我打赌他在这里甚至都不合法
I mean, I'll bet he's not even here legally.
哦 我的上帝
Oh, my God.
什么 现在你需要绿卡才能被绑架？
What, now you need a green card to be fucking abducted?
你知道我在说什么 我的意思是 他甚至不应该在这里
You know what I'm saying. I mean, he shouldn't even be here.
这有什么关系？
What does that matter?
问他在这个国家是否合法
Ask him if he was in the country legally.
问问他
Ask him.
啊 看到了吗？
Ah, see?
- 来吧 没关系 - 当然可以
- Come on. It doesn't matter. -Sure it does.
这家伙可能在家得宝门前闲逛
This guy was probably hanging out in front of The Home Depot
与其他20名非法外国人在一起
with 20 other illegal aliens.
无论什么
Whatever.
当我们逃离船只时
While we were running away from the ships,
他朝他们跑去 “Trabajo！Trabajo”
he was running towards 'em going, "Trabajo! Trabajo!"
混蛋 这些家伙为了最低工资拼命工作
Asshole, these guys work their asses off for barely minimum wage.
夺走美国人民的工作
Taking American people's jobs.
我们开始了 嗯？
Here we go, huh?
什么 你认为我工作不努力？
What, you don't think I work hard?
是的 我肯定你的街角办公室真的很烦人
Yeah, I'm sure your corner office is a real drag.
嘿嘿
Hey. Hey.
- 谁 我？ - 是的 我不认识你吗？
- Who, me? - Yeah, don't I know you?
- 啊！我想知道为什么  - 不 真的
- Huh! I wonder why. - No, seriously.
他问我们是否认识这里的人 我认识他
He asked if we knew anyone in here. I know him.
我不认识你 伙计
I don't know you, man.
你是北好莱坞的机械师
You're a mechanic in North Hollywood.
劳尔 劳尔·希门尼斯 我记得你
Raul. Raul Jimenez. I remember you.
- 他做了什么 - 我没做什么 他在撒谎 伙计
-What'd he do? -I didn't do shit. He's lying, man.
他把女朋友打得屁滚尿流
He beat the shit out of his girlfriend.
真的很糟糕 至少我认为是他的女朋友
Really bad. At least I think it was his girlfriend.
- 希望不会再有了 - 来吧 伙计 真的吗？
-Hopefully not any more. -Come on, man. Serious?
你确定是他吗？
Are you sure it was him?
是 啊我记得他 因为他右眼下面的纹身
Yeah. I remember him 'cause of that tattoo under his right eye.
那滴眼泪 看到了吗？
That teardrop. See it?
- 操你 伙计  - 这是干什么的？
- Fuck you, man. - What's it for?
这是给我表哥的 他中枪了 像你这样的猪
It's for my cousin. He got shot. By a pig like you.
是的 你们是罪犯是我的错
Yeah, and it's my fault you guys are criminals.
- 他16岁  - 街上少了一个罪犯
- He was 16. - One less criminal on the street.
操你 伙计
Fuck you, man.
- 这是真的还是假的 - 关于他的表哥？我不知道
-Is it true or not? -About his cousin? I don't know.
- 不 关于他  - 是的 这是真的 告诉他们
- No, about him. - Yeah, it's true. Tell them.
告诉他们你是怎么打败她的
Tell them how you beat the shit out of her.
这不是第一次 也不会是最后一次
And it wasn't the first time and it won't be the last time, either.
告诉他们！
Tell 'em!
好吧 也许我们不应该在这里刻板印象
Okay, maybe we shouldn't stereotype in here.
婊子得到了她应得的 伙计
Bitch got what she deserved, man.
他在那里 看到了吗？这些混蛋 伙计 这些混蛋从不学习
There he is, see? These assholes. Man, these assholes never learn.
她不应该在我身上乱搞 伙计
She shouldn't have fucked around on me, man.
这样就可以把她打得屁滚尿流了
Like that makes it okay to beat the shit out of her.
哦 是吗？你打算怎么办 伙计？
Oh, yeah? What are you gonna do, man?
你要杀了我吗 猪？
You gonna shoot me, huh, pig?
我想我不需要
I don't think I need to.
认识其他人吗？
Recognize anyone else?
- 不 我不这么认为  - 是的 还有其他人吗？
- No, I don't think so. - -Yeah, anybody else?
未付停车罚单？
Unpaid parking tickets?
- 如果这很重要呢 - 嗯？
-What if that's important? -Huh?
喜欢也许我们应该弄清楚谁好谁坏
Like... maybe we're supposed to figure out who's good and who's bad.
世界不是这样的 亲爱的
World doesn't work that way, sweetheart.
这是正确的 灰色区域太多
That's right. Too much gray area.
但也许这就是他们希望我们做的
But maybe that's what they want us to do.
杀死某些人
Kill off certain people.
我的天 谁来决定？你
And like, oh, my God, who's gonna decide? You?
不 不是我 我们所有人 作为一个团体
No, not me. All of us, as a group.
我们已经在做了
Kind of what we're doing already.
一点都没有阻止这一切
Kind of not stopping this whole thing at all.
我们不知道 可能
We don't know that. It might.
这一切背后一定有原因 对吧？
There has to be a reason behind all of this, right?
哦 我的天 亲爱的
Oh, my God, sweetheart.
不是这个世界上发生的每一件事
Not every shitty thing that happens in this world
背后一定有原因
has to have a reason behind it.
也许他们只是想看着我们互相残杀
Maybe they just wanna fucking watch us kill each other.
嗯 我们至少应该考虑一下
Well, we should at least consider it.
考虑一下什么？
Consider what?
她的意思是…谁值得活着？
What she means is... who deserves to live?
可以基于什么？
Okay. Based on what?
基于一切
Based on everything.
道德 价值观 你一生中做过或没有做过的事
Morals, values, what you have or haven't done in life.
我认为我们需要把一切都放在那里
I think we need to put it all out there.
我们有很多时间站在那里讨论每个人的性格
We got plenty of time standing around debating everybody's character.
我们是来做点什么的
Well, we're here to do something.
这就是死亡
It's to die.
嘿 嘿 我有个主意
Hey, hey, I got an idea.
我们   我们下一步杀了所有黑人怎么样？
How about we... How about we kill all the black people next, yeah?
你在说什么？
What are you talking about?
别打比赛牌 伙计 这只是他妈的机会
Don't play the race card, man. This is all just fucking chance.
是 啊正确的这就是为什么我们大多数人都死了 对吧？
Yeah? Right. That's why most of us are dead, right?
这里每个人都是为了自己
It's every man for himself in here.
是的 你需要闭嘴 不要说这些种族主义的东西 好吗？
Yeah, you need to shut up with this racism stuff, okay?
- 这里没人在乎 - 我在这附近拉屎
-Nobody gives a shit around here. -I give a shit around here.
听着 我只是说 我不会下一个 好吗？
Look, I'm just saying, I'm not fucking next, all right?
你们都达到了少数派配额
Y'all done reached your minority quota.
这很公平
That's fair.
这家伙 伙计 你看到这里发生了什么事吗？
This guy. Man, you see anything fair going on in here?
这和公平完全相反！
This is the exact fucking opposite of fair!
可以我们拭目以待
Okay. We'll see.
别看我 伙计 这是你惹的祸
Don't look at me, man. You started this shit.
来吧 兄弟 你知道我是对的
Come on, man. You know I'm right, bro.
想想看
Think about it.
他们会把我们每个人都杀掉 直到我们一个都不剩
They'll kill each and every one of us off until there's none of us left.
来吧 伙计 很多白人也死了
Come on, man. Plenty of white people are dead too.
来吧 伙计 还有很多人还活着
Come on, man. There's plenty more still alive too.
你到底想用这个做什么？让自己成为目标？
What exactly are you trying to do with this? Make yourself a target?
因为这正是你在做的
Because that's exactly what you're doing.
是的 真聪明
Yeah, real smart.
你看不到我在数亚洲人
You don't see me counting Asians.
- 也许你应该试试 - 不要相信这种种族主义的废话
-Well, maybe you should try. -Don't fall for this racism bullshit.
他只是想拯救自己的屁股
He's just trying to save his own ass.
你他妈的对 你这个紧张的混蛋 那又怎么样？
You damn right, you uptight asshole. So what?
所以 什么 你觉得你应该得到免费通行证 因为你他妈的是黑人？
So, what, you feel like you deserve a free pass because you're fucking black?
没人在乎
Nobody cares.
确切地没人在乎
Exactly. Nobody gives a shit.
- 我不是在和你的蠢驴说话 - 我是在帮你 兄弟！
-I ain't talking to your stupid ass. -I'm trying to help you, bro!
你他妈的闭嘴 伙计
You shut the fuck up talking to me, man.
这他妈的帮不了你
It's not gonna fucking help you in here.
对 因为它通常会帮助我 对吧？
Right, 'cause it usually helps me out there, right?
我们来了 让我们都为黑人感到难过
Here we go. Let's all feel bad for the black guy.
因为他比我们还要挣扎
'Cause he had to struggle so much more than we did.
好吧 放下它
All right, just drop it.
像你们一样 人们得不到足够的帮助
Like you people don't get enough help.
- 你他妈的刚刚说什么？ - 你们都一样
- What the fuck you just say? - -You guys are all the same.
你到处跑 你只想让别人给你东西
You run around, you just want people to hand you things
就像你他妈的赚了一样
like you fucking earned it.
这就是这个国家现在的问题所在
That's what's wrong with this country now.
社会主义胡说八道
Socialist bullshit.
什么你也想要一些赔偿吗？
What? You want some reparations too?
我的意思是 天啊 给我他妈的在这里休息一下！
I mean, Jesus Christ, give me a fucking break around here!
我认为我们需要避免个人偏见
I think we need to keep our personal prejudices out of this.
- 这无助于局势  - 他们不再重要了
- It's not helping the situation. - -They don't matter any more.
不 不 见鬼 不 它们对我来说绝对重要
No, no, hell, no, they absolutely matter, to me.
我不会为了一些种族主义者的生存而死去
I'm not gonna die so some racist can live.
一切 每一件事都需要摆在桌子上
Everything, every single thing needs to be out there on the table.
是的 所以如果我们能让所有种族主义者挺身而出 那就太好了
Yeah, so if we could have all the racists step forward, that'd be great.
听着 不管你的种族 民族 国籍 这都不重要
Look, whatever your race, ethnicity, nationality, it's not important.
重要的是 我们要共同找出如何阻止这种情况
What's important is that collectively we figure out how to stop this.
- 我们是同一个团队 - 不过 我们是吗？
-We're on the same team here. -Are we, though?
- 我们都想活着 不是吗？ - 是 啊
- We all wanna live, don't we? - Yeah.
所以让我们一起努力 我们不能一直反目成仇
So let's work together. We can't keep turning against each other.
- 是的 这就是他们希望我们做的  - 我认为她是对的
- Yeah, that's what they want us to do. - -I think she's right.
这就是为什么 他们想让我们玩他们的小游戏
That's what this about. They want us to play their little game.
- 也许他们现在正在监视我们  - 研究我们
- Maybe they're watching us right now. - -Studying us.
- 我们不要给他们想要的  - 确切地
- Let's not give them what they want. - -Exactly.
有什么想法吗？
Any ideas?
如果我们强行打平会怎么样？
What happens if we force a tie?
- 我们试过了  - 我们尽量不投票
- We tried that. - -We tried not voting at all.
两回合之间会有更多的时间
There'd be more time between rounds.
好吧 每个人都为自己投票
Okay, everybody vote for yourself.
我们如何做到这一点？
How do we do that?
嗯 你不能为自己投票 它不允许我们
Well, you can't vote for yourself. It doesn't let us.
好吧 那么大家都投票给你右边的人
All right, then everybody vote for the person to your right, then.
- 活着的人  - 不要投票给空位
- The living person. - -Don't vote for empty spaces.
如果我们做对了 我们都应该得到一票
If we do it right, we should all get exactly one vote.
可以
Okay.
十 九 八 七
Ten, nine, eight, seven,
六 五 四
six, five, four,
三 二 一
three, two, one...
- 不 - 噢 操！
-No! -Oh, fuck!
- 该死 - 它不起作用
-Damn it! -It didn't work.
- 发生了什么 - 我们搞砸了
-What happened? -We screwed up.
让我们再试一次
Let's try it again.
这行不通 他们想到了一切！
It won't work. They thought of everything!
你投票给你右边的人还是左边的人？
Did you vote for the person to your right or your left?
我这样做是对的
I did right, this way.
有人搞砸了
Well, somebody messed it up.
有人搞错了
Somebody just made a mistake.
好吧 听着 我们必须再试一次
Okay, look, we have to try this again.
好吧这次非常小心
All right. Very carefully this time.
每个人都投票给指向你右边那个人的箭头
Everybody vote for the arrow that points to the person on your right.
知道了？
Got it?
亲爱的 你看到那支箭了吗？
Sweetie, you see that arrow?
这个箭头 你会   你会选箭的 好吗？
This arrow. You're gonna... You're gonna pick that arrow, okay?
你没事 不 我们都会没事的 我保证 可以
You're okay. No, we're all gonna be okay, I promise. Okay?
来吧
Come on!
这是一条领带 大家再次投票！
It's a tie. Everyone vote again!
他妈的刚刚发生了什么？
What the fuck just happened?
- 他们打成平手  - 怎样
- They tied. - How?
我们都得到了相同的票数 对吧？
We all got the same number of votes, right?
不 我们没有
No, we didn't.
你怎么知道的？
How do you know?
因为我投了他的票
'Cause I voted for him.
- 你是什么 - 你为什么要这样做？
-What are you... -Why would you do that?
因为他投票给了怀孕的女孩 我看见他了
Because he voted for the pregnant girl. I saw him.
如果我不投票给他 她就死了
If I didn't vote for him, she'd be dead.
- 你确定吗？ - 对
- You sure? - Yes.
他为什么要那样做？
Why would he do that?
听着 我们都知道我们不能为自己投票 对吧？
Look, we all know that we can't vote for ourselves, right?
你觉得会发生什么
Well, what do you think happens
当我们找到最后一个人的时候？
when we get down to the last person left?
我们中的一个人可以活下来
One of us gets to live.
这是一场比赛 这是一个淘汰的过程
It's a game. It's process of elimination.
最后一个站着的人可以活着离开这里
The last man standing gets to walk out of here alive.
或者女人
Or woman.
他们为什么要这样做？
Why would they do that?
我不知道
I don't know.
但在孩子和怀孕的女孩之间 我相信那家伙认为
But between the kid and the pregnant girl, I'm sure that guy figured
最终很可能会落到其中一个身上
it's most likely gonna come down to one of them in the end.
如果我们除掉他们 我们都会有更好的机会
If we get rid of them, we'll all have a better chance.
你知道吗？如果他是对的 如果我们中的一个人真的能离开这里
You know what? If he's right. If one of us do get to walk out of here,
它应该是其中之一
it should be one of them.
- 为什么因为这是常识
-Why's that? -'Cause it's common sense.
各位 别这样 这里的情况不同
People, come on. Things are different in here.
妇女和儿童优先？我很抱歉 但那狗屎已经不重要了
Women and children first? I'm sorry, but that shit doesn't matter any more.
看看这位孕妇 她算作两个人
Look at the pregnant woman. She counts as two people.
其中一个人最终会死 所以
One of them's gonna die eventually, so...
哪一个？
Which one?
没关系 没关系 一切都会好起来的
It's okay. It's okay. It's gonna be okay.
不不
No! No!
- 不 - 加油 加油 加油
-No! -Come on, come on, come on.
- 不要做任何事 - 他们都会死的
-Don't do anything. -They'll both die.
我们必须知道发生了什么
We have to know what happens.
你们这些人怎么了？
What is wrong with you people?
她只是个孩子 你为什么要追她？
She's just a kid. Why would you go after her?
他们中的一个必须死 我们需要做出决定
Well, one of 'em has to die. We need to decide.
不 我们没有
No, we don't.
我们应该尽可能地把他们排除在外
We should just leave 'em out of this for as long as possible.
- 让我们忘掉这件事吧  - 不 我们不能这样做 不能再这样了
-Let's just forget about it. -No, we can't do that, not any more.
- 为什么不？ - 这对他们来说太危险了
- Why not? - It's too dangerous for them.
- 他们已经暴露了 - 来吧
-They've been exposed. -Come on.
没有人会再次投票给他们 对吧？
No one is going to vote for them again, right?
她从没听说过节育 所以她能活下来？
She's never heard of birth control, so she gets to live?
我们需要在每次淘汰之前做出多数决定
We need to come to a majority decision before each elimination
否则他们会一直处于危险之中
otherwise they are constantly gonna be in jeopardy.
他是对的 我们现在需要保护他们
He's right. We need to protect them now.
我们甚至不知道她是个什么样的孩子
We don't even know what kind of a kid she is.
我是说 如果她是个可怜的孩子呢？
I mean, what if she's a miserable brat?
- 她大概十岁 - 嘿 孩子 你成绩好吗？
-She's like ten. -Hey, kid. You get good grades?
- 嗯 - 是 啊直As？
-Uh-huh. -Yeah. Straight As?
天啊 她得了B 我们杀了她吧
Oh, my God, she got a B. Let's kill her.
听着 他们中至少有一个人会死的
Look, at least one of them is gonna have to die.
所以我们应该现在就决定
So we should decide now.
把他们都杀了 他妈的杀了他们
Just kill 'em both. Just fucking kill 'em...
志愿者呢？
What about volunteers?
- 什么？ - 志愿者？
- What? - Volunteers?
你疯了吗？
Are you nuts?
我不知道 也许有人想挺身而出
I don't know. Maybe someone wants to step forward.
我会做的
I'll do it.
- 为什么？ - 现在 等一下
- Why? - Now, wait a minute.
他不必告诉你或其他人原因
He doesn't have to tell you or anybody else why.
他是自愿的 够了
He's volunteered. That's enough.
我想知道为什么
I wanna know why.
女士 这不关你的事
Lady, it's none of your business.
嘿 让他回答
Hey, let him answer.
为什么？
Why?
我想我只是不想杀人
I guess I just don't wanna kill anyone.
- 你多大了 - 16.
-How old are you? -16.
- 没有 其他人 - 你是什么意思 别人？
-No. Someone else. -What do you mean, someone else?
- 他他妈的是个孩子 - 他16岁 那已经够老了
-He's a fucking kid, man. -He's 16. That's old enough.
- 到什么年纪了 会死吗 - 自己做决定
-Old enough to what, to die? -To make your own decisions.
他是个愚蠢的孩子 他一点也不知道
He's a stupid kid. He doesn't know any better.
我不在乎 如果你自愿 你就自愿
I don't care. If you volunteer, you volunteer.
- 如果他想死 那是他的选择 - 是的 是的 没错
-It's his choice if he wants to die. -Yeah, yeah, that's right.
如果有人想做志愿者 无论是谁 我们都应该尊重这一点
If someone wants to volunteer, we should respect that, no matter who it is.
儿子 你叫什么名字？
Son, what's your name?
- 我是肖恩 - 肖恩
-I'm Shaun. -Shaun.
你确定你想做志愿者吗？
Are you sure that you wanna volunteer?
不
No.
我会做的
I'll do it.
没事的
It's fine.
好吧 如果我们能找到几个志愿者 这会容易很多
Well, this is gonna be a whole lot easier if we can get a few volunteers.
谁更容易？你
Easier for who? You?
听着 我们必须控制   这是最好的办法
Look, we gotta take control of the... the situation, and this is the best way.
我的意思是 嘿 如果我们都要死了 那还不如按照我们自己的方式
I mean, hey, if we're all gonna die, it might as well be on our own terms.
是的 是的 这会教那些该死的外星人
Yeah, yeah, that'll teach those fucking aliens.
嘿 我们正在尽我们所能 伙计
Hey, we're doing what we can, man.
是的 这是我们最好的主意
Yeah, it's the best idea we got.
- 然后你自愿加入 - 我看不到你向前走
-Then you volunteer. -I don't see you stepping forward.
我们都应该向前迈进 我的意思是 除了她 所有人
We should all step forward. I mean, everybody but her.
那么大规模自杀呢？太好了 让我们这样做吧
So mass suicide, then? That's great. Let's do that.
嘿 孩子 你还想当志愿者吗？
Hey, kid, you still wanna volunteer?
不
No.
对
Yes.
你是他妈的英雄 孩子 你知道吗？
You're a fucking hero, kid, you know that?
- 是的 对  - 不是 我是认真的
- Yeah, right. - No, I'm serious.
听着 如果我能离开这里 我会以你的名字命名我的下一个孩子
Look, if I make it out of here, I'm naming my next kid after you.
- 谢谢 斯科特 - 谢谢你 斯科特
-Thanks, Scott. -Thank you, Scott.
他妈的混蛋 你知道他的名字叫肖恩
Fucking assholes. You knew his name was Shaun.
- 随便 这孩子是个英雄  - 他给了我们两分钟的时间
- Whatever. The kid's a hero. - He bought us two minutes.
- 有人扔给他一颗紫心 - 好了 够了
-Somebody toss him a Purple Heart. -All right, enough.
什么你为什么看着我？
What? What are you looking at me for?
你觉得应该是我？
You think it should be me?
过去两年我在阿富汗
I was in Afghanistan for the past two years
冒着生命危险保护你们其他人的安全
risking my life to keep the rest of you safe.
我两天前刚回来
I just got back two days ago.
我在去看家人的路上
I was on my way to see my family.
我有一个七个月大的
I got a seven-month-old...
他甚至不知道我是谁
who doesn't even know who I am.
我妻子
My wife...
我没见过我妻子在
I haven't seen my wife in...
我他妈的不会死在这里 我不是
I'm not fucking dying in here. I'm not.
我要回家了
I'm going home to them.
别担心 我不会投票给你
Don't worry. I'm not voting for you.
我也是
Me neither.
是的 我们要离开这里 伙计
Yeah, we're gonna get out of here, man.
- 是的 当然  - 来吧 伙计
- Yeah, sure we are. - Come on, man.
不 你来吧 伙计 他知道真相
No, you come on, man. He knows the truth.
- 我们都知道 让我们接受它  - 停下来
-We all do. Let's just accept it. -Just stop.
你会死的 伙计 我们都是
You're gonna die, dude. We all are.
- 时间不多了 - 是 啊我们仍然需要一名志愿者
- Time is running out. -Yeah. We still need a volunteer.
任何人
Anybody.
我是志愿者
I volunteer.
我的儿子奥斯卡
My son, Oscar,
他去年去世了
he passed away last year.
他骑着摩托车
He was riding his motorcycle.
没关系
It's okay.
我原谅她
I forgive her.
- 你会再见到他的 - 你觉得呢？
-You'll see him again. -You think?
绝对地
Absolutely.
可以
Okay.
我平静地去
I go in peace.
再见 各位
Bye, everybody.
- 再见 - 再见
-Goodbye. -Goodbye.
再见
Goodbye.
“你会再次看到他 当然 ”
"You'll seem him again. Absolutely."
- 胡说  - 是的 真的
- Bullshit. - Yeah, seriously.
他只是想在她生命的最后时刻给她一些平静
He was just trying to give her some peace in her last moments of life.
这没什么错
There's nothing wrong with that.
她牺牲了自己 让别人活下去 这不会被忽视
She sacrificed herself so that others could live. That doesn't go unnoticed.
- 谁说的 - 上帝说
-Says who? -Says God.
- 你怎么知道的 - 我是部长
-How do you know? -I'm a minister.
上帝在监视我们所有人
God is watching over all of us.
他有一个计划 我们只需要有信心
He has a plan. We just have to have faith.
- 阿门  - 够了 伙计
- Amen. - Enough, man.
我很抱歉？
I'm sorry?
恕我直言   那只是扯淡
With all due respect... that's just bullshit.
站在那里谈论信仰
Standing around there talking about faith
当人们被炸得左右为难的时候
when people are being blasted to shit left and right.
- 这他妈的太荒谬了  - 嘿 伙计
- That's fucking ridiculous. - Hey, man...
如果有上帝 他对我们任何人都不在乎！
If there is a God, he doesn't give a shit about any of us!
- 这不是真的 - 天啊 我们都快死在这里了
-That's not true. -Oh, my God, we're all dying in here.
这该死的事不会结束 直到这个混蛋把我们都弄到手 好吗？
This shit's not gonna end until this motherfucker gets all of us, okay?
所以你想相信什么？相信这一点！
So you wanna have faith in something? Have faith in this!
可以因为上帝在这里 对吧？
Okay? Because that's God in here now, right?
那是上帝 就在这里
That's God, right now, in here.
所以 向他祈祷或问他 甚至更好
So pray to him or ask him, even better.
我是说 上帝 你说什么？
I mean, what does thou sayeth, God?
我们当中谁会去你的神圣王国？
Who among us will get to go to your divine kingdom?
- 嘿 别紧张  - 还是怎样
- Hey, take it easy. - Or what?
你他妈的要杀了我 因为我有意见？
You gonna fucking kill me 'cause I have an opinion?
和你的一样有效 伙计
Just as valid as yours, man.
事实上 环顾这个房间 我想我可能有一些朋友
Looking around this room, actually, I think I might have some friends.
我想人们都同意我的观点
I think people agree with me.
95%的人相信上帝 你是少数
95 percent of people believe in God. You're in the minority.
是的 95%的人都是白痴
Yeah, well, 95 percent of people are idiots.
你在叫我们白痴吗？
Are you calling us idiots?
我不会叫任何人白痴 好吗？我只想说这个
I'm not calling anybody idiots, all right? All I'm saying is this.
如果有上帝 这是什么   这看起来他会允许吗？
If there is a God, is this something... Does this seem like he would allow this?
这是他会做的吗？
Is this something he would do?
你们这些混蛋会杀了我 因为你们害怕我是对的？
You fuckers are gonna kill me because you're afraid I'm right?
你在做什么？你他妈的是懦夫 嗯？
What are you doing? You're fucking cowards, huh?
请稍等 我甚至没有说错话
Wait, please. I didn't even say anything wrong.
- 他做到了 - 这他妈的是谁？
-He did. -Who the fuck is this?
看起来上帝刚刚给了你一个机会
Looks like God just cut you a break.
是的 再过两分钟
Yeah, for another two fucking minutes.
伙计们 我认识这个女孩 我不认识你吗？
Guys, I know this girl. Don't I know you?
是的 是的 是的 我在某个地方认识你
Yeah, yeah. Yeah, I know you from somewhere.
- 我 - 是 啊你是女演员吗？
-Me? -Yeah. Are you an actress?
你太熟悉了
You're so familiar.
不 我不是演员
No, I'm not an actress.
是 是 是 史黛西有事
Yeah, yeah, yeah. Stacy something.
- 不 克里斯蒂娜 - 克里斯蒂娜
-No, Christina. -Christina...
- 克里斯蒂娜 - 是 啊
-Christina? -Yeah.
等一下 那么史黛西是你的艺名吗？
Wait a minute. Is Stacy your stage name, then?
不 我告诉过你 我不是演员
No, I told you, I'm not an actress.
这就是事实 对吧
That's what it is, right.
男人 演员 色情明星 我现在明白了
Guys, actress, porn star. I get it now.
这是一个巨大的差异
It's a huge difference.
什么我不是色情明星
What? I'm not a porn star.
嘿 我想没有人在乎   你知道吗？
Hey, I don't think anybody cares around... around here, you know?
我是说 我以前就是想不通 现在我知道了
I mean, I just couldn't figure it out before. Now I know.
- 什么？ - 我是个超级粉丝
- What? - I'm a huge fan.
你他妈的在干什么？我不做色情
What the fuck are you doing? I don't do porn.
我不认为这是个问题 每个人都要谋生
I don't think it's a problem. Everybody's gotta make a living.
- 我没问题 - 我不做色情
-I don't have a problem with it. -I don't do porn.
好吧 随便 我只是想恭维她
All right, whatever. I'm just trying to pay her a compliment.
他在撒谎
He's lying.
我必须对你说实话 你知道 我的意思是
I gotta be honest with you, you know, I mean,
不过 在你增强之前 我确实更喜欢你
I did like you better, though, before your enhancements,
因为现在就像是 “砰！看看这些坏孩子 ”
because now it's just like, "Wha-bam! Look at these bad boys."
- 他在撒谎  - 它们是真的吗？
- He's lying. - Are they real?
- 这不关你的事 - 你是说它们是真的吗？
-That is none of your fucking business. -Are you saying they're real?
那又怎么样？洛杉矶一半的女孩都有大胸部
So what? Half the girls in LA have big boobs.
是的 我相信这对生意很好
Yeah, and I'm sure it's great for business.
- 我不做色情 - 谁为他们买单？
-I don't do porn! -Who paid for them?
告诉他们 去吧
Tell them, go ahead.
没事的 亲爱的 谁为他们买单？是你的雇主吗？
It's okay, sweetheart. Who paid for them? Was it your employer?
- 没有 - 不
-No. -No?
- 我是说 他做到了 - 是吗？
-I mean, he did. -He did?
但事实并非如此
But it's not like that.
现在很难做出决定
Now it's getting really difficult to decide.
不 大卫是我的老板 但我们也是
No, David is my boss, but we're also...
- 我不是 - 嗯
-I am not... -Uh-huh.
你看 史黛西在这里想 如果她得了双D
You see, Stacy over here thought if she gets those double Ds,
大卫会爱上她的
David's gonna love her.
我是说 他会爱她胜过爱自己的妻子和孩子
I mean, he's gonna love her way more than his own wife and kids.
我是说 谁在乎他们是否已经是一家人了？
I mean, who cares if they're already a family?
它从未阻止过你 是吗？
It's never stopped you before, has it?
什么 你要和他私奔吗？
What, are you gonna run off with him?
你自己会有一堆孩子吗？
Gonna have a bunch of kids on your own?
在海边安顿下来？
Settle down by the beach?
这就是你要做的吗 史黛西？
Is that what you're gonna do, Stacy?
我认为我们应该考虑到人们是否有家庭
I think we should take into account if people have families.
儿童
Children.
为什么？你有几个孩子？
Why? How many kids do you have?
我有七个
I have seven.
- 你当然知道  - 是的 我有12个
-Of course you do. -Yeah, I got 12.
- 是的 我27岁 - 现在 现在 来吧 认真地
-Yeah, I got 27. -Now, now, come on, seriously.
这难道不应该被考虑在内吗？
Shouldn't that be taken into consideration?
- 是的 是的 我们有一个女儿 - 是 啊艾米丽
-Yeah. Yeah, we have a daughter. -Yeah. Emily.
- 她三岁 - 我们都有家人
-She's three. -We all got families.
你的孩子救不了你
Your kids ain't gonna save you in here.
嘿 我不是要求被救 我…我只是说
Hey, and I'm not asking to be saved. I... I'm just saying...
如果你没有孩子
if you don't have children,
也许你应该做志愿者 我认为这是合理的
maybe you should volunteer. I think that's reasonable.
是的 也许我们中的一些人有一天想要孩子
Yeah, well, maybe some of us wanna have kids someday.
是啊 我还是个孩子
Yeah, well, I still am a kid.
是的 我也是
Yeah, me too.
我认为如果你没有孩子
And I think that if you don't have children,
你应该做正确的事 向前走
you should do the right thing and step forward.
你多大了？
How old are you?
什么 我？但我有个孩子
What, me? 35. But I have a kid.
- 只有一个孩子 - 是的 一个女儿
-Just one child? -Yeah, a daughter.
- 你结婚了 - 对
-You married? -Yes.
- 你丈夫是做什么的 - 我不
-What does your husband do? -I don't...
你不知道什么？
You don't what?
为什么突然对我感兴趣？
Why the sudden interest in me?
我们都是诚实的 我只是想问你一个问题
We're all just being honest. I just thought I'd ask you a question.
嗯 我没有受审 那你告诉我们你的生活怎么样？
Well, I'm not on trial, so how about you tell us about your life?
容易的41.
Easy. 41.
我有两个男孩 一个18个月大的女儿
I've got two boys, an 18-month-old baby daughter.
和同一个了不起的女人结婚12年了 嗯
Been married to the same amazing woman for 12 years. Erm...
就这样 轮到你了
That's it. Your turn.
倒霉
Shit.
仍在等待
Still waiting.
我抚养了我的四个弟弟妹妹
I raised my four younger siblings
在我父亲的海洛因成瘾和母亲的临床抑郁症期间
during my father's heroin addiction and mother's clinical depression,
然后以工作/学习奖学金进入瓦萨
then attended Vassar under a work/study scholarship
在尼泊尔和平队服役三年之前
before serving in the Peace Corps for three years in Nepal
然后回到美国 从那以后我一直为一家非盈利机构工作
and then returned to the US where I've worked for a non-profit ever since.
好吧 但你仍然没有回答我的问题
Okay, but you still haven't answered my question.
- 你丈夫是做什么的 - 我有一个妻子
-What does your husband do? -I have a wife.
哦所以你是女同性恋
Oh! So you're a lesbian.
是 啊那又怎么样？没什么区别
Yeah. So what? Doesn't make any difference.
这不一定是真的
That's not necessarily true.
所以她是同性恋 了不起的事怎么了
So she's gay. Big deal. What's the matter?
你觉得一个孩子和两个同性恋妈妈一起长大可以吗？
You think it's okay for a child to be raised with two gay moms?
这不是他妈的1950年 伙计
It's not fucking 1950, dude.
是的 说真的 管好你自己的事
Yeah, seriously, mind your own business.
什么 你觉得在这样的环境中抚养一个女婴没关系吗？
What, you think it's okay to raise a baby girl in that environment?
两个同性恋妈妈到处做爱？
Two gay moms having sex all over the place?
这不像两个人那么糟糕 但还是错了
It's not as bad as two men, but it's still wrong.
也许你在这里是件好事
Maybe it's a good thing that you're here.
你会给那个小女孩一个正常生活的机会
You're gonna give that little girl a chance to have a normal life.
哇 来吧 伙计 你要拿这个去哪里？
Whoa, come on, man. Where are you going with this?
- 我不是同性恋或其他什么… - 是的 对
- I'm not homophobic or anything... - -Yeah, right.
你认为这是值得为之而死的人吗？
Do you think that this is someone worth dying for?
我知道你们很多人都很虔诚
I know a lot of you are religious.
这个国家以家庭价值观为基础
This country was based on family values.
这是一个犯了罪的女人
This is a woman who has sinned.
这不意味着什么吗？
Doesn't that mean something?
- 我们都犯了罪 - 是的 但有些人比其他人多
-We've all sinned. -Yes, but some more than others.
我的意思是 也许这就是这件事的全部意义
I mean, maybe that's the whole point of this thing.
也许如果我们弄清楚罪人是谁
Maybe if we figure out who the sinner is amongst us
也许这一切都会结束
that maybe this whole thing will end.
我的意思是 我们不知道这些外星人想要什么
I mean, we have no idea what these aliens want.
我的意思是 也许这就是答案
I mean, maybe that's the answer.
所以外星人想让我死因为我是同性恋？
So aliens want me to die because I'm gay?
听着 没什么私人的 我只是想让这一切停止
Look, nothing personal. I'm just trying to get this to stop.
你认为只有我一个人？
You think I'm the only one?
胆小鬼
Cowards.
我儿子是同性恋
My son's gay.
他一点毛病都没有
And there's not a damn thing wrong with him.
- 如果他有道理呢？ - 把它放下就好了
- What if he had a point? - Just drop it already.
不 不 不是关于同性恋的事
No, no, not about the gay stuff.
我的意思是 如果我们中的一个人死了 他们想要的那个人 而这一切都结束了呢？
I mean, what if one of us dies, the one they want, and this all ends?
上帝啊我们一直在兜圈子
Jesus. We just keep going in circles.
他们为什么要把我们中的一个挑出来？
Why would they single one of us out?
我们有一个问题
We have a problem.
什么
What?
这个人说我们中的一个人可能会活着离开这里 对吧？
Well, this guy said that one of us might make it out of here alive, right?
- 是的 - 因为我们不能为自己投票
-Yeah. -Because we can't vote for ourselves.
正确的
Right.
我想知道会发生什么
Well, I'd like to know what's gonna happen
当只剩下两个人的时候
when there's only two people left.
什么意思？
What do you mean?
如果只剩下两个人 你只能投票给另一个人
If there's only two people left, you can only vote for the other person.
- 妈的 他们会打平的 - 他们都会死
-Shit, they would tie. -And they would both die.
不 不 不 不一定 一个人不必投票
No. No, no, no. Not necessarily. One person doesn't have to vote.
- 什么 - 一种牺牲
-What? -A sacrifice.
- 是的 - 这是什么意思？
-Yes. -What does that mean?
这意味着 如果我们中的一个人和他们中的一个 我们就不会投票
It means that if it comes down to one of us and one of them, we don't vote.
有人必须牺牲自己来拯救另一个人
Somebody would have to sacrifice themself to save the other.
是的 对 谁会这么做？
Yeah, right. And who would do that?
我会的
I would.
- 你当然会的  - 我会的 你不会吗？
- Sure you would. - I would. Wouldn't you?
我真的不知道我会做什么
I really don't know what I would do.
那就让我们希望它不会落到你身上
Let's hope it doesn't come down to you, then.
至少他是诚实的
At least he's being honest.
在这里 真相会让你丧命
In here the truth gets you killed.
在这里 一切都会让你丧命
In here everything gets you killed.
我们应该选择一个我们可以信任的人
We should pick someone we can trust.
我们不能相信这里的任何人 我想我们现在已经知道了
We can't trust anyone in here. I think we know that by now.
总得有人来做 我们应该决定
Well, somebody's gonna have to do it. We should decide.
我们不必做任何决定
We don't have to decide anything.
不管最后剩下谁都会做出决定
Whoever's left in the end will make that decision.
如果归结到他们两个呢？
What if it comes down to the two of them?
那么 他们必须做出决定
Well, then, they'll have to decide.
或者我们可以为他们做决定
Or we can decide for them.
你不应该嫁给那个混蛋
You should have never married that asshole.
我知道
I know.
在一起
Together?
怎么搞的？
What happened?
- 他们打成平手  - 多么浪漫
- They tied. - How romantic.
我想如果没有人投票 它是随机选择的
I thought if no one voted, it chose randomly.
我想不是打领带
Not in a tie, I guess.
看见他们都活不下去了 这意味着其中一人必须离开
See? They both can't live. That means one of them has to go.
- 他们哪儿也不去  - 其中一人必须死亡
- They're not going anywhere. - One of them has to die.
你们想让他们决定吗？
You guys want them to decide?
一个小孩？这对一个孩子来说责任太大了
A little kid? That's too much responsibility for a child.
是的 他是对的 我们需要成为做这件事的人
Yeah, he's right. We need to be the ones to do it.
- 做什么 - 他想让我们杀了其中一个
-Do what? -He wants us to kill one of them.
我只是说我们做了需要做的事
I'm just saying we do what needs to be done.
瞎扯！你只是想救你自己
Bullshit! You're just trying to save your own fucking ass.
它救不了我也救不了你
It doesn't save me any more than it saves you,
但它保证我们中的一个人会活着离开这里
but it guarantees that one of us will make it out of here alive,
否则我们都会死
otherwise we will all die.
听着 这是个骗局 好吗？
Listen, this is a trick, all right?
一旦他让其中一个让开 他就会去追另一个
Once he gets one of them out of the way, he'll just go after the other.
不要相信他的胡说八道
Don't fall for his bullshit.
如果我们必须从中选择一个   会是谁？
If we had to choose one of 'em... who would it be?
你是做什么的？
What do you do?
- 什么？ - 来吧 伙计
- What? - Come on, man.
嘿 这是个公平的问题
Hey, it's a fair question.
- 你是什么意思 比如工作 - 是 啊
-What do you mean, like for work? -Yeah.
当然 是那个穿毛衣背心的家伙开始上课了
Of course it'd be the guy in the sweater vest to start this class bullshit.
嘿 嘿 嘿我们正在努力决定谁应该活着 对吧？
Hey, hey, hey, we're trying to decide who deserves to live, right?
职业选择是实现这一目标的途径
And career choice is the way to do that.
我只是想说 有些人比其他人对社会的贡献更大
I'm just saying that some people contribute more to society than others.
谁在乎她做什么？她怀孕了 这才是最重要的
Who cares what she does? She's pregnant, that's what matters.
有很多婴儿 我的意思是 人们有很多孩子
There are plenty of babies. I mean, people have lots of babies.
世界上有足够的单亲妈妈靠福利生活
The world has enough single moms on welfare.
- 她可能失业了 - 那又怎么样？
-She might be unemployed. -So what?
这没关系
That doesn't matter.
你丈夫是做什么的？
What does your husband do?
- 什么 - 爸爸 宝贝爸爸
-What? -The daddy. The baby daddy.
他是做什么的？
What does he do?
你知道父亲是谁吗？
Do you even know who the father is?
- 是的 我知道父亲是谁  - 是的 但你还没结婚 是吗？
-Yes, I know who the father is. -Yeah, but you aren't married, huh?
听着 他   我们在等待
Look, he's... We're waiting.
等待什么？让他出狱？
Waiting for what? For him to get out of prison?
- 得了吧 - 他没进监狱
-Oh, come on. -He's not in jail.
好吧 那么他是做什么为生的？
Okay, so what does he do for a living, then?
调查已经够了
Enough with the inquisition.
你是做什么的？
What do you do?
- 我在银行工作  - 你当然知道
- I work for a bank. - -Of course you do.
我们借钱给人们创业
We lend people money to start their own businesses.
这里有人有自己的生意吗？
Does anybody here have their own business?
- 你去年赚了多少钱 - 我说的不是薪水
-How much did you make last year? -I'm not talking about salaries.
你是那个开始谈论工作的人
You were the one that started talking about the jobs.
不 我说的是成为社会的贡献者
No, I'm talking about being a contributing member of society.
现在 我每天都在拼命工作
Now, I work my ass off every single day
我从不 从不接受任何人的施舍
and I never, never take handouts from anyone.
我借钱给人们实现他们的梦想
I lend people money to live their dreams.
在工作之外 我为慈善事业贡献了大量资金
And outside of work I contribute a significant amount of money to charity.
好吧 当你把数字降到六位数时 这很容易
Well, that's easy when you're pulling down six figures.
哦 嗯 你是做什么的？
Oh, uh-huh, and what do you do?
- 我是一名研究生 - 嗯 在里面
-I'm a graduate student. -Uh-huh. In?
心理学
Psychology.
嗯 这很有用 你呢？你是做什么的？
Well, that's useful. How about you? What do you do?
- 滚开 笨蛋 - 你是做什么的？
-Fuck off, dickhead. -What do you do?
你领取残疾支票了吗？
You collect your disability checks?
听着 伙计 如果你想让我们不要投票给你
Listen, guy, if you're trying to get us to not vote for you,
你走错了路
you're going about it the wrong way.
- 说真的  - 看 看 看
- Seriously. - Look, look, look.
我们需要提出一些度量标准
We need to come up with some sort of metric here.
某种方式来决定谁活着
Some way to decide who lives.
我所知道的是 如果我们中的一个人能活下来 那将是这两个人中的一个
All I know is if one of us gets to live, it's gonna be one of those two,
至少如果我对此有什么想说的话
at least if I have anything to say about it.
我想我们都知道这意味着什么
Well, I think we all know what that means.
是的 是的 他是对的 她走了 他应该是下一个
Yeah, yeah, he's right. She's gone. He should be next.
太好了 两对一
How nice. Two for one.
- 说真的 - 我是说 总得有人走 对吧？
-Seriously. -I mean, somebody has to go, right?
你没看到他们在这里做什么吗？
Don't you see what they're doing here?
他们只是杀了她 让多数人重新回到他们的立场
They just killed her to get the majority back in their favor.
- 他们知道她站在我们这边 - 哪一边？
-They knew that she was on our side. -What side?
- 是的 这里没有任何边 - 真正地
-Yeah, there aren't any sides here. -Really?
所以你从来没有投票给他们两个？
So you've never voted for the two of them?
- 不 当然不是 - 瞎扯
-No, of course not. -Bullshit.
你不知道谁在这里投票给谁 我们谁也不知道
You don't know who's voting for who in here. None of us do.
我认为我们有一个很好的主意
I think we have a pretty good idea.
请大家 如果他们让大多数人站在自己一边
People, please, if they get the majority back on their side,
他们会杀了他们两个
they will kill both of them.
这就是他们想要的 让他们让开
That's what they want, to get them out of the way.
只有我们其他人才能阻止这种情况的发生
Only the rest of us can stop that from happening.
你太偏执了 伙计
You're paranoid, man.
好吧 谁和我在一起？两个女孩加上我   那是三个
Okay, who's with me? The two girls plus me, that's... that's three.
我们这里还剩16个人 我们只需要再加六个就能到九个
There's 16 of us left in here. We just need six more to get to nine.
- 够了 - 九什么？
-That's enough. -Nine what?
- 九票赞成多数票 - 确切地
-Nine votes for a majority. -Exactly.
我加入了
I'm in.
很好 很好 还有五个
Good, good. Five more.
- 大家都明白吗 - 这太疯狂了 这是行不通的
-Everybody understand? -This is crazy. It's not gonna work.
好吧 我进去了
All right, I'm in.
- 我也是  - 好的 那是六个 我们还需要三个
-So am I. -Okay, that's six. We need three more.
你们呢？
What about you guys?
你到底要我们做什么？
What exactly are you asking us to do?
- 我们请求你帮助我们  - 是的 但怎么做？
-We're asking you to help us. -Yeah, but how?
听着 他们每次都会投票给这两个女孩中的一个
Look, they are gonna vote for one of those two girls each and every time.
最终他们会得到他们想要的
Eventually they're gonna get what they want.
- 除非我们阻止他们  - 怎么阻止他们？
- Unless we stop them. - Stop them how?
- 通过分组投票 - 是的 伙计 这只是在防守
-By block voting. -Yeah, man, it's just playing defense.
- 他是对的 没有其他办法 - 现在只是一场数字游戏
-He's right, there's no other way. -It's just a numbers game now.
这太荒谬了！
This is ridiculous!
你和我在一起吗？
Are you with me?
我们该怎么做？
What do we do?
这一轮没有人投票支持他们 好吗？
No one's voting for them this round, okay?
是的 我们说的是一个不会说英语的人
Yeah, we said the guy who doesn't speak any English.
他现在帮不了我们 所以一旦他走了 我们都可以讨论下一步该做什么
He can't help us now, so once he's gone, we can all discuss what to do next.
你们都知道需要做什么！
You all know what needs to be done!
为孩子投票 这是我们唯一的机会！
Vote for the kid. It's the only chance that we have!
该死的！
Goddamn it!
你他妈的很可怜 你会杀一个孩子来救自己的命
You're fucking pathetic, man. You'd kill a kid to save your own life.
没错 我想和你一样生活
That's right, I wanna live, just like you.
不 不只是像我一样 我不会那样做的
No, not just like me. I wouldn't do that.
哦 是的 好吧 我们会看看你在网上的时候会做什么
Oh, yeah, well, we'll see what you do when it's your ass on the line.
不 我想你不会的
No, I don't think you will.
这是什么意思？什么 你现在要杀了我？
What's that supposed to mean, huh? What, you're gonna kill me now?
为什么？因为我想活下去 嗯？
Why? Because I wanna live, huh?
我是个他妈的坏人 因为我不想死在这里？
I'm a fucking bad person because I don't wanna fucking die in here?
你知道吗？好的
Well, you know what? Fine.
你想玩游戏吗？我会玩你的游戏
You wanna play games? I'll play your game.
我说我们现在就把他们两个都处理掉 从孩子开始
I say we get rid of both of them right now, starting with the kid.
这让我们都有机会活着离开这里
That gives us all a chance to walk out of here alive.
现在 我知道我不是这里唯一一个想这样做的人
Now, I know I'm not the only one in here that wants to do that.
他是对的 我们还剩15个人
He's right. There's 15 of us left.
我们只需要六个人来平衡比赛场地
All we need is six to even the playing field.
- 这不是游戏 - 不 不是
-This isn't a game. -No, it's not.
但当你选边的时候 你决定把它变成一场比赛
But you decided to make it a game when you chose sides.
嗯 我们选择了 我们只是选择了一方 即这里的每个人都是平等的
Well, we chose. We just chose the side that said everyone in here is equal.
没有人是特别的 你们所有人都应该明白这一点
No one's special. You of all people should understand that.
- 嘿 你 你不爱你的妻子吗 - 我当然知道
-Hey, you. Don't you love your wife? -Of course I do.
你不想给她一个离开这里的机会吗？
Well, don't you want to give her a chance to get out of here?
如果你站在他们一边怎么会这样？
How's that gonna happen if you're on their side?
听他说
Listen to him.
如果你选择他们一方 你就等于判你妻子死刑
If you choose their side, you're just sentencing your wife to death.
我们的方式会给她一个生存的机会
Our way will give her a chance to live.
- 对 - 我
-Right. -I...
- 是的 是的 但是 - 但什么都没有！
-Yeah, yeah, but... -But nothing!
你想不想救她？
Do you wanna save her or not?
好 好 好！我们进去了！
Okay, okay, fine! We're in!
- 我也是 - 什么
-Me too. -What?
我们都是平等的 他是对的
We're all equal. He's right.
- 什么 - 可以那是   那是五
-What? -Okay. That's... That's five.
我们只需要三个
We just need three more.
- 每个人都投票给这个孩子  - 我们投票给你
- Everybody vote for the kid. - We're voting for you.
来吧 伙计们 你不想活下去吗？
Come on, people. Don't you wanna live?
好了 让他们再打一次 他们都会死的 这很公平
All right, make them tie again. They'll both die. That's fair.
- 什么 - 他是对的 我们会接受这种交易
-What? -He's right. We'll take that trade.
- 你在做什么 - 别这样 她是个孩子！
- What are you doing? -Don't do it. She's a kid!
性交 刚刚发生了什么？
Fuck. What just happened?
你输了 混蛋
You lost, assholes.
操你 他们为什么不打领带？
Fuck you. Why didn't they tie?
为什么他们第一次打成平手而不是第二次？
Why did they tie the first time and not the second?
有人改变了他们的投票
Somebody changed their vote.
谁
Who?
你为什么不问问你妻子？
Why don't you ask your wife?
- 是你吗 - 不
-It was you? -No.
我是说 是的 但是
I mean, yes, but...
你为什么要换人？
Why'd you switch?
我没有 我只是没有第二次投票
I didn't. I just didn't vote the second time.
我不能 我很抱歉
I couldn't. I'm sorry.
对 因为你是个好人
Right, because you're a good person.
嘿 别插手 好吗？
Hey, stay out of this, okay?
听着 女士 没人说这会很容易
Look, listen, lady, nobody said this was going to be easy,
但这需要做
but it needs to be done.
是的 听着 反正他们都活不下去了
Yeah, listen, they both can't live anyway.
他是对的 他们中的一个最终将不得不死去
He's right. One of them is going to have to die eventually.
我们需要团结起来 否则他们会赢的
We need to band together, otherwise they're gonna win.
这里没有胜算 我们都输了 好吗？这很好
There's no winning here, man. We all lose, okay? And that's fine.
我们有足够的时间来接受这一点
We've had plenty of time to accept that.
我们只能做一件事
There's only one thing left that we can do,
那就体面地离开这里
and that's go out of here with some dignity.
也许我们可以救两个人而不是一个人
And maybe we can save two people instead of one.
他不是在说她
He's not talking about her.
他说的是尽快获得K - I - D的R - I - D
He's talking about getting R-I-D of the K-I-D sooner rather than later.
- 我想她会拼写  - 我们只需要解决这个问题
- Think she can spell. - We just need to get this over with.
撕开创可贴 为什么要拖出来？
Rip the Band-Aid off. Why drag it out?
- 你寡不敌众 - 没错 一切都结束了
-You're outnumbered, man. -That's right. It's over.
可以
Okay.
你想活下去 对吧？
You wanna live, right?
是 啊
Yeah.
- 但我不 - 想杀一个小孩 没关系
-But I don't... -Wanna kill a little kid. It's okay.
好吧 每个人都投票给那个单臂的人
Fine, everybody vote for the guy with one arm.
- 哦 求求你了 伙计  - 不 不 听 听
-Oh, please, man. -No, no, no, listen, listen.
如果我们除掉他 事情就会平复
If we get rid of him, it'll even things out
我们会有更多的时间来讨论这个问题
and we'll actually have more time to talk about this.
没什么好说的了
There's nothing left to talk about.
听着 你只是想给自己争取更多时间
Listen, you're just trying to buy yourself more time.
我想给大家争取一些时间
I'm trying to buy everybody some time.
好吧 刚才发生了什么？
All right, what the hell just happened?
这是什么意思？
What does that mean?
这意味着形势已经改变了 婊子
It means the tables have turned, bitch.
人们开始看清事情
People are starting to see things clearly.
是谁干的？
Who did that?
下一个是大兵乔 他是团队的领导者
GI Joe next. He's the leader of the pack.
先杀了他 剩下的就完蛋了
Kill him first, the rest'll cave.
好主意 我们只剩下13个人了 我们只需要七个
Great idea. There's only 13 of us left. We only need seven.
我们该怎么做？
What do we do?
你无能为力 我们现在占了多数
There's nothing you can do. We've got the majority now.
让我们投票给她
Let's vote for her.
- 什么 - 他想保护她？
-What? -He wants to protect her?
- 让我们考验一下他吧 - 嘿 嘿 嘿 等等 好吗？
-Let's put him to the test. -Hey, hey, hey. Wait a minute, okay?
- 每个人都这么做 他会改变的 - 不 等等 给我一秒钟
-Everybody do it. He'll switch. -No, wait. Give me a second.
- 讲道理 伙计 - 我讲道理了
-Be reasonable, man. -I am being reasonable.
- 你想给你妻子一个机会吗 - 是 啊
-You wanna give your wife a chance? -Yeah.
然后做正确的事情
Then do the right thing.
- 否则她还有30秒的生命 - 不
-Otherwise she's got 30 seconds to live. -No!
这里没有正确的东西
There's no right thing in here.
是的 有 我们都知道
Yes, there is. We all know it.
听着 你杀了我 你会死的 她会死的
Listen, you kill me, you'll die and she'll die next.
我们都知道这一点
We all know that.
- 来吧 - 你爱不爱你妻子？
-Come on. -Do you love your wife or not?
拜托！
Come on, please!
妈的 好的 是的 我会改变的！他妈的选别人！
Fuck, okay, yes, I'll switch! Fucking pick somebody else!
- 等等 等等 - 每个人都投票给黑人
-Wait, wait, wait. -Everybody vote for the black guy.
等等 什么？操你们 伙计！
Wait, what? Fuck y'all, man!
当然真爱征服一切
Of course. True love conquers all.
你别无选择 我的朋友
You're out of options, my friend.
是 啊你们都自杀了 祝贺
Yeah? Well, you all just killed yourselves. Congratulations.
你 你 你 你们都做到了
You, you, you. You all did this.
和你   你刚刚杀了你的妻子
And you... You just killed your wife.
- 我希望你幸福 - 我做了我必须做的事
-I hope you're happy. -I did what I had to do.
是的 现在她会因为你而死去
Yeah, well, now she's gonna die because of you.
至少我的方式给了她一个机会
At least my way gave her a chance.
- 闭嘴 伙计  - 是的 伙计 放下它
- Just shut the fuck up, man. - -Yeah, man, just drop it.
- 他们可能还没有结婚 - 什么
-They're probably not even married. -What?
我是说 想想看
I mean, think about it.
他们是这里唯一一对已婚夫妇的几率有多大？
What are the odds of them being the only married couple in here?
另外两个人认识
Those other two knew each other.
- 他们说 - 那不行 伙计
-So they said. -That's not gonna work, dude.
你是说他们结婚了
So you're saying that they're married
而他们恰好就在一起？
and they just happen to be placed right next to each other?
嗯 大家想想看
Uh-uh. Think about it, people.
难道不可能是他们编造的吗？
Isn't it possible that they just made this whole thing up?
- 没有 - 他们为什么要撒谎？
- No. - Why would they lie?
为了生存 没有人想杀死某人的妻子或丈夫
To survive. Nobody wants to kill someone's wife or husband.
尤其是在彼此面前
Especially right in front of each other.
他们只是为了得到我们的同情而编造了这件事
They just made this whole thing up to get our sympathy.
- 你疯了 - 是吗？
-You're crazy. -Am I?
你结婚多久了？
How long have you been married?
- 五年 - 他的父母叫什么名字？
-Five years. -What's his parents' names?
- 嗯   马克和丽莎 - 她在哪里上的大学？
-Erm... Mark and Lisa. -Where'd she go to college?
UCLA公司
UCLA.
他的生日是什么时候？
When's his birthday?
- 呃…四月  - 四月
- Er... April. - April...
第9位 4月9日
9th. April 9th.
他叫什么名字？
What's his name?
什么
What?
你丈夫叫什么名字？
What is your husband's name?
- 他已经说出了他的名字  - 没错 他做到了
- He already said his name. - -That's right, he did.
- 什么时候 - 他第一次说话
-When? -The first time he spoke.
他说出了他的名字
He said his name.
放下它 伙计 好吗？
Just drop it, man, okay?
他叫什么名字？
What's his name?
- 她不知道  - 她当然没有
- She doesn't know. - Of course she doesn't.
是的 她当然会
Yes, of course she does.
她只是不想玩你的游戏！
She's just not gonna play your fucking games!
让我们把他们绑起来 看看会发生什么
Let's put 'em in a tie and see what happens.
什么
What?
如果他们结婚了 他们不可能投票给对方
If they're married, there's no way they will vote for each other.
可以我们编的
Okay. We made it up.
- 但这是她妈的主意 - 什么
-But it was her fucking idea. -What?
是的 是的 我只是同意了
Yeah, yeah. I just went along with it.
不 他是先说的 我与此事无关
No, he said it first. I had nothing to do with it.
- 来吧！她是个骗子 看看她 - 请不要杀了我
-Come on! She's a liar. Look at her. -Please don't kill me.
不 杀了这个婊子！
No, kill this bitch!
- 你为什么哭 - 闭嘴 好吗？
-Why are you crying? -Just shut the fuck up, all right?
你不应该对我们撒谎
You shouldn't have lied to us.
我没有撒谎
I didn't lie.
是的 你做到了 你说你结婚了
Yes, you did. You said you were married.
我结婚了 只是没有和他结婚 我确实有一个女儿 艾米丽
I am married, just not to him. And I do have a daughter, Emily.
我没有撒谎
I didn't lie about that.
你认为有多少人结婚 有丈夫 有妻子 有孩子？
How many people do you think were married, had husbands, wives kids?
你杀了他们中的任何一个都没有问题
You had no problem with killing any of them.
- 我没有杀他们  - 是的 你做到了
- I didn't kill them. - Yes, you did.
我们都做到了
We all did.
但是 听着 你还有机会离开这里
But, listen, you still have a chance to make it out of here.
我们还剩11个人 我们只需要六票
There's 11 of us left. We just need six votes.
如果你加入我们的行列 我保证会让你活着
If you join our side, I promise I will keep you alive.
别听他的 他只是想利用你
Don't listen to him. He's just trying to use you.
嘿 你想离开这里吗？
Hey, you wanna get out of here?
你想回家看看你真正的丈夫 见到艾米丽吗？
You wanna go back home and see your real husband, see Emily?
是 啊
Yeah.
好的
Good.
你呢？你站在谁一边？
How about you? Whose side are you on?
什么 你不说话？
What, you don't speak?
好吧 他不想告诉我们他投票给谁
Okay, he doesn't wanna tell us who he's voting for,
这很好 我理解
and that's fine, I understand that.
没有人想在这里树敌
Nobody wants to make enemies in here.
我要继续说 他站在我们这边
I'm gonna go ahead and say that he's on our side.
你有一个女儿 是吗？她叫什么名字？
You have a daughter, don't you? What's her name?
克洛伊
Chloe.
这是一个美丽的名字 克洛伊
That's a beautiful name, Chloe.
- 你想再见到她吗 - 明显地
-You wanna see her again? -Obviously.
- 你的搭档呢 - 妻子
-And your partner? -Wife.
- 阿米莉亚 - 克洛伊和阿米莉亚
-Amelia. -Chloe and Amelia.
你想再见到他们吗？
Do you wanna see both of them again?
- 对不起 - 等一下 等一下
- I'm sorry. -Wait a minute. Wait a minute.
嘿 那是五个 我们只需要多一个
Hey, that's five. We just need one more.
- 来吧 伙计们 再来一个 - 我们投票给谁？
-Come on, people. One more. -Who are we voting for?
- 那个军人 - 不选择其他人
-The army guy. -No! Pick somebody else.
- 癌症女士 - 什么
-Cancer lady. -What?
不 不 不 好吧 你们都知道该投票给谁
No, no, no. All right, you all know who to vote for.
倒霉！
Shit!
性交 好吧
Fuck. All right.
性交
Fuck.
天啊
Holy shit.
我们该怎么做？
What do we do?
听着 没关系 没关系
Listen, it's okay. It's okay.
好了 我们还剩七个人 我们只需要四个
Okay, there's seven of us left. All we need is four.
一 二 三
One, two, three...
是男孩还是女孩？
Is it a boy or a girl?
我不知道
I don't know.
你不想知道吗？
Don't you wanna find out?
是的 我当然知道
Yes, of course I do.
只需一票
All it takes is one vote.
真的很简单 就一次
It's really that simple. Just once.
不
No.
不 请不要
No, don't, please.
请
Please.
- 求你了 - 不 不 我不会这样做
-Please. -No, no, I won't do it.
我不会这么做的
I will not do it.
那么 你在杀害自己的孩子
Well, then, you're killing your own child.
你呢 伙计？你想活下去吗？
How about you, man? You wanna live?
你知道我的立场
You know where I stand.
- 你呢 - 耶稣基督
-What about you? -Jesus Christ.
你怎么认为？
What do you think?
请原谅我
Forgive me.
不不要！
No! Don't!
对耶稣基督 谢谢你 耶稣
Yes! Jesus Christ. Thank you, Jesus.
那个好吧 所以   三比三
That... Okay, so it's... There's three to three.
你现在无法保护他们
There's no way you can protect them now.
是 啊好吧 我们拭目以待
Yeah? Okay, well, we'll see about that.
你知道是你还是他们 对吧？
You realize that it's you or them, right?
- 那就这样吧 - 你在做志愿者？
-So be it. -You're volunteering?
如果我走 你就走
If I go, you go.
可以这个怎么样？我会跟你做个交易
Okay. How about this? I'll make you a deal.
你给我一个 我给你她
You give me one of them and I'll give you her.
- 什么？ - 我们会交易的
- What? - We'll trade.
你想要哪一个？
Which one do you want?
任何一个 对我来说无关紧要
Either one. Doesn't matter to me.
什么你在做什么？
What? What are you doing?
好吧 成交 处理
Okay, deal. Deal.
你得到了小女孩 我得到了假妻子
You get the little girl, I get the phony wife.
我们三个会投票给她 你们三个会投她
The three of us will vote for her, the three of you will vote for her.
- 我怎么知道我可以信任你 - 不
-How do I know I can trust you? -No.
我们将   我们将按顺序投票
We'll... We'll vote in order.
一 二 三
One, two, three.
- 好吧 成交 - 等等
-Okay, deal. -Wait a second.
没关系 听着 相信我 只是
It's okay. Listen, trust me, just...
好的 我先去
Okay, I'll go first.
- 必须有信任 - 我不知道这件事
-There must be trust. -I don't know about this.
没关系 没关系 我带你走了这么远
It's okay. It's okay. I got you this far.
- 好的 - 我们来做吧
-Okay. -Let's do it.
可以
Okay.
- 你在做什么 - 想做就做
-What are you doing? -Just do it.
不 不
No, no.
好了 现在是她
Okay, now her.
好了 轮到你了 去
Okay, it's your turn. Go.
嘿 走吧 轮到你了
Hey, go. It's your turn.
- 你在做什么？轮到你了 - 你在做什么？
-What are you doing? It's your turn. -What are you doing?
- 来吧 伙计 投票  - 匆忙
- Come on, man, vote. - Hurry!
- 你在做什么？为孩子投票 - 选票
-What are you doing? Vote for the kid. -Vote!
- 你疯了吗？投票 - 请投票！请投票！
- Are you nuts? Vote! -Vote, please! Please vote!
- 他在干什么？投票 - 你在做什么？来吧 投票
-What's he doing? Vote. -What are you doing? Come on, vote.
请投票！选票
Please vote! Vote!
耶稣基督 你为什么不投票？
Jesus Christ. Why didn't you vote?
因为他不投票
Because he doesn't vote.
- 从来没有 一次也没有  - 什么
- Never has, not once. - What?
他从来没有说过一句话 从来没有投票 他一直都在努力
He's never even said a word, never voted, and he's made it all this way.
该死的运气
Dumb fucking luck.
大概
Maybe.
也许不是
Maybe not.
什么
What?
- 也许这不是意外 - 你在说什么？
-Maybe it was no accident. -What are you talking about?
我认为他还活着是有原因的
I think that there's a reason why he's still alive.
是的 因为他一直躲着 希望我们不会注意到他
Yeah, because he's been hiding, hoping we wouldn't notice him.
你猜怎么着 伙计？你的时间到了
Well, guess what, buddy? Your time's up.
你无处藏身
There's nowhere left for you to hide.
不 不 我不认为是这样
No. No, I don't think that's it.
然后呢？
Then what?
想想看 他是这里唯一一个从未投票的人
Think about it. He's the only person in here who has never voted.
所以他活了这么久只是因为他没有参加？
So he's survived this long just because he hasn't participated?
我不知道 可以是
I don't know. Could be.
这就是所有这些的答案？
That's the answer to all this?
那么…什么是   这意味着什么 他   他能活下去吗？
So... what does... what does that mean, that he... he gets to live?
大概
Maybe.
这让他无法接触吗？
Does that make him untouchable?
有一种方法可以确定
There's one way to know for sure.
是 啊让我们看看会发生什么
Yeah. Let's see what happens.
如果我们投票给他 也许这一切都会停止
If we vote for him, maybe all this will stop.
来吧
Come on.
等待
Wait...
所以这一切都是你编造的？
So you made all that up?
不 不 他从来没有投票 我不这么认为
No, no. He's never voted. I don't think so.
至少 他从未说过一句话
At least, that and he's never said a word.
我的意思是 我不记得了
I mean, not that I can remember.
我认为他不想给他们任何东西
I don't think he wants to give them anything.
我们已经给他们足够了
We've already given them enough.
你想让我们投票给你吗？
Do you want us to vote for you?
他知道我们别无选择
He knows we don't have a choice.
他们为什么要这样对待我们？
Why are they doing this to us?
我想这是一种实验
It's some kind of experiment, I guess.
就这样？
And that's it?
是的 也许 我是说 也许他们只是想了解我们
Yeah, maybe. I mean, maybe they just wanted to learn about us.
了解什么？
Learn what?
我不知道
I don't know.
也许只是为了看看我们会做什么
Maybe just to see what we would do
以及我们会选择谁以及为什么
and who we would choose and why.
为了什么？
For what?
了解我们 我们看重什么 我们不看重什么 对我们来说重要什么
To understand us, what we value, what we don't, what matters to us.
让我们互相残杀
By making us kill each other.
当我们杀人时 我们在评判他们
When we kill someone, we're judging them
我们说他们有问题
and we're saying that there's something wrong with them.
我想这就是他们一直在寻找的
I think that's what they've been looking for.
那么我们现在该怎么办？
So what do we do now?
这取决于你们两个
That's up to the two of you.
- 但我们该如何选择呢 - 我不知道
-But how do we choose? -I don't know.
但一旦我走了 你们中的一个必须挺身而出
But once I'm gone, one of you is gonna have to step forward,
否则你们两个都会死
otherwise you'll both die.
但你必须自己决定 我不能为你做这件事
But you're gonna have to decide for yourselves. I can't do it for you.
你没有多少时间
You don't have much time.
我要走了
I'll go.
- 为了孩子 对吧 - 嗯
-For the baby, right? -Uh-huh.
你真勇敢
It's very brave of you.
你叫什么名字？
What's your name?
- 凯蒂 - 好了 凯蒂 我们一起去 好吗？
-Katie. -Okay, Katie, we'll go together, okay?
可以可以
Okay. Okay.
它必须以这种方式结束
It has to end this way.
没有更多的时间了 做吧！
There's no more time. Do it!
性交 来吧
Fuck. Come on.
当然
Of course.
当然所有这些
Of course. All that...
这一切都是徒劳的
All that for nothing.
所有这些 怎么了？
All that. What's the matter, huh?
什么 我对你不够好？
What, I'm not good enough for you?
什么我不是你想要的那个人？
What? I'm not the one that you wanted?
我和这里的其他人完全一样
I'm exactly the same as everybody else in here.
他们都必须做出自己的选择
They all got to make their own choices.
他们选择了互相残杀
They chose to kill each other.
这就是你想看到的 对吧？嗯？
That's what you wanted to see, right? Huh?
好了 恭喜你 我们是混蛋
Well, there you go, congratulations. We're assholes.
操你
Fuck you.
我们都知道我们不能为自己投票 对吧？
We all know that we can't vote for ourselves, right?
你觉得会发生什么
Well, what do you think happens
当我们找到最后一个人的时候？
when we get down to the last person left?
这是一场比赛 这是一个淘汰的过程
It's a game. It's process of elimination.
最后一个站着的人可以活着离开这里
The last man standing gets to walk out of here alive.
在孩子和怀孕的女孩之间
Between the kid and the pregnant girl,
我相信最终最有可能是他们中的一个
I'm sure it's most likely gonna come down to one of them in the end.
你必须自己决定 我不能为你做这件事
You're gonna have to decide for yourselves. I can't do it for you.
它必须以这种方式结束
It has to end this way.
你没有多少时间
You don't have much time.